Guide to the Rice University KTRU Radio records, 1962-2018 UA 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Audio recordings, 1968-2007, 59004
  - Sub-Series: 1981/1982, 59368
    - News Archive 2, 1981-10-31-1982-01-22; wrc07191; 59372 (Box 14)
      Contents include: (00:01) Political rally at RMC Grand Hall for Kathy Whitmire, Lane Lalor, George Greanias; (02:24) Sheriff Jack Heard on election night; (03:02) Louis Macey on election night; (03:30) Lance Lalor on election night; (05:45) November faculty meeting; (07:40) Moral Majority Debate in RMC Grand Hall; (08:21) Rev. Billy Graham's crusade at Rice Stadium; (09:10) Sports and weather; (09:55) Texas A and M student suspended for sword; (10:26) Will Rice College names Pres. Ronald Reagan honorary member; (11:25) Sports review/preview; (13:58) Dr. Jean-Claude De Braemaker interview on Mayor Kathy Whitmire posters; (15:26) Lance Lalor wins City Controller; (16:58) George Greanias wins City Council District C; (17:54) Kathy Whitmire mayoral campaign worker interview; (18:03) Lance Lalor on voter turnout; (18:22) NCAA bowl predictions; (20:25) Sports review/preview; (22:49) SA Senate meeting review; (23:57) Sports review/preview; (24:53) Wiess College becoming tamer; (26:32) Sports review/preview; (28:43) NBC News visits Rice for student reaction to draft registration; (29:54) Leonardo Da Vinci exhibit at Sewall Gallery; (30:37) Snow at Rice; (31:44) Hanszen College fire; (33:12) Room and Board increase; (34:46) Rice student Margaret Fossi found dead; (35:44) The Judy's; (36:07) SA Secretary vacancy; (36:34) Space Shuttle Columbia; (37:08) Sports preview; (38:20) C.R.A.P. Creative Radio Announcement Programming; (39:42) Ralph Records 10th anniversary; (41:30) Bad News. We adjusted the speed from 41:30 to the end. Speakers: Dave Collins, George Greanias, Jack Heard, Louis Macey, Lance Lalor, Debbie Gronke, James Groves, Jonathon Sadow, David Tuttle, Jean-Claude de Braemaker, Cindy Childers, Lynn Lednicky, Greg Roberts
    - George Greanias political ads, 1981-10; wrc07949 (Box 14)
      Contents include: Three political ads for George Greanias, running for City Council District C. We deleted extraneous audio at the beginning of this recording. Speakers: George Greanias
    - Chicken Skin Music - The Banded Geckos (2 reels), 1981-11-03; wrc08259_01; wrc08259_02 (Box 14)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," the Banded Geckos perform. Speakers: Tim Taylor, Evelyne Taylor, Russell Fory, Gary Young, David John Scribner
    - Moral Majority debate, 1981-11-09; wrc07999 (Box 14)
      Contents include: Dr. William Martin moderates a forum with David Berg and Cal Thomas debating the moral majority and related issues pertaining to the inclusion of religious ideas in government. Speakers: Cal Thomas, David Berg, William Martin
    - To the Point - Allen Matusow, 1981-11-12; wrc07192 (Box 14)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Allen Matusow about the potential resurgence of politicals radicals. Speakers: Allen Matusow, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Don Clayton, 1981-11-12; wrc07193 (Box 14)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Don Clayton about the nature the universe. Speakers: Don Clayton, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Frank Fisher, 1981-11-12; wrc07194 (Box 14)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Frank Fisher about the harmful effects of lead shot in the bird population. This tape suffered from sticky shed syndrome and thus has playback issues. We have altered the recording to normalize the speed. Speakers: Frank Fisher, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Sarah Hrdy, 1981-11-12; wrc07195 (Box 14)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Sarah Hrdy about the women's movement. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Sarah Hrdy
    - The Fleshtones interview, 1981-11-14; wrc07196; 59404 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Jim Fowler and Michael F. Zakes talk to members of The Fleshtones about the band history, touring and performing, London, and recording their new album. The interview includes songs from the Action Dogs a side project for Jan Marek Pakulski and a station ID. Speakers: Bill Milhizer, Peter Zaremba, Keith Streng, Gordon Spaeth, Jim Fowler, Michael F. Zakes, Jan Marek Pakulski
    - Robert Fripp interview, 1981-11-15; wrc07197; 59405 (Box 15)
      Contents include: C. Kemp interviews Robert Fripp about restarting King Crimson, touring, communication and interviews, goal as a musician, music composition, and his upcoming album. Speakers: Robert Fripp, C Kemp
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1981-11-24; wrc07950 (Box 15)
      Contents include: The Rice Jazz Ensemble performs at Hamman Hall under the direction of Ken Dye with guest artist Larry Slezak. This recording has technical difficulties. We deleted radio music during the performance's intermission. Performers: Ken Dye, Larry Slezak, Grant Gist, John Godwin, John McDaniel, Germaine Petry
    - To the Point - David Parsons, 1981-12-10; wrc07198 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. David Parsons about his face casting project with the world's tallest woman. Speakers: David Parsons, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Esther de Vecsey, 1981-12-10; wrc07199 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Esther de Vecsey about the Leonardo Da Vinci exhibition and the artist. Speakers: Esther de Vecsey, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1981-12-10; wrc07200 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the changing attitudes of opinionn polls. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Stephen Klineberg
    - To the Point - Susan and Roderick McIntosh, 1981-12-10; wrc07201 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Susan and Roderick McIntosh about archeological finds in west Africa. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Susan McIntosh, Roderick McIntosh
    - Roky Erickson with the Resurrectionists interview, 1981-12-21; wrc07202; 59402 (Box 15)
      Contents include: The interviewer talks to Roky Erickson and the Resurrectionists about their musical style, about the 13th Floor Elevators, favorite artists, other albums, and their set list. We deleted extraneous audio at the beginning, middle, and end of the recording. Speakers: Roky Erickson, Jimmy Jones, Brian Curley, Carl Giesecke
    - 10 Year Anniversary promo, 1981; wrc07975 (Box 15)
      Contents include: A promo made up of other recordings in celebration of KTRU's 10th anniversary.
    - Chicken Skin Music - Clairseach, 1981; wrc08256 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Charlie and Ann Heymann talk about how they find their songs, the history of the Gaelic harp, and their musical experience. Speakers: Charlie Heymann, Ann Heymann, David John Scribner
    - Owlman, 1981; wrc07994 (Box 15)
      Contents include: An episode of "Owlman," satirical superhero student radio show about Rice University, about interest free loans and parking regulations. Speakers: Stan Barber, John Gladu, David Hoehl, Karen Pieper, Sharon Hughes, Paul Williamson, Greg Cagle
    - Herschel Berry and the Natives, 1981; wrc08006 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Studio recording of Herschel Berry and the Natives. We deleted radio music at the end of the recording. Speakers: Herschel Berry, Wylie hudgins, Kenn Cordray, Karl Logan
    - To the Point - Gale Stokes, 1982-01-12; wrc07203 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Gale Stokes about Poland from a historical perspective. Speakers: Gale Stokes, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - John Boles, 1982-01-12; wrc07204 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. John Boles about slavery and the church. Speakers: John Boles, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Julie Taylor, 1982-01-12; wrc07205 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Julie Taylor about the roles of men and women in Latin society, especially Eva Perón. Speakers: Julie Taylor, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Linda Adair, 1982-01-12; wrc07206 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Linda Adair about the rise in breastfeeding. Speakers: Linda Adair, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Peter Papademetriou, 1982-01-19; wrc07207 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Peter Papademetriou about the effects of tall buildings in Houston. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Peter Papademetriou
    - The Third Wave live, 1982-01-23; wrc07208; 59384 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Rice University student band Third Wave live at the Rice Memorial Center Grand Hall.
    - The Judy's live, 1982-01-23; wrc07209; 59429 (Box 15)
      Contents include: The Judy's live at the Grand Hall of the Rice Memorial Center. Ends abruptly. Speakers: David B. Bean, Dane Cessac, Jeff Walton
    - News Archive 3, 1982-01-25-1982-03-22; wrc07210; 59373 (Box 15)
      Contents include: (00:01) Reward for killer/s of Margaret Fossi; (01:07) Pres. Ronald Reagan's "State of the Union"; (03:18) Baker College issuing parking tickets; (04:36) Brig. Gen. James Dozier rescued from Italian terrorists; (05:04) TexPIRG hires Jim Koenig as advisor; (05:48) C.R.A.P. Creative Radio Announcement Programming; (06:59) Telefund report; (07:30) Student Association elections; (08:15) ICSA fire; (08:35) Yves Klein exhibit; (09:17) Sam Houston State University fire; (10:04) Eleanor Evans basket weaving exhibit; (11:58) International Students Organization meeting; (12:39) Rice College Bowl team 2nd in regional tournament; (13:22) Unknown team; (13:58) Jim Koenig on TexPIRG; (14:39) Late filing candidates to SA positions; (16:08) Lynn Ashby at Lovett College; (18:16) James Robison at Morality Forum at RMC; (20:24) Student athletic fee increase; (21:22) Dr. Herbert Ganz speaking at Rice; (22:01) TexPIRG on blanket tax; (22:23) KTRU requests increase of blanket tax; (23:14) Owlcon III; (24:28) Sports review/preview; (25:41) SA elections; (26:10) Phi Beta Kappa; (27:42) Rice Women's Basketball win over Texas Lutheran TAIAW Division II; (29:37) TAIAW II Playoffs; (32:04) Jupiter Effect; (32:52) SA elections report; (33:35) New College Masters: Jones, Brown, Will Rice, Hanszen; (34:14) Rice tennis; (34:25) Tornadoes and survival tips; (35:28) Wiess College election results; (36:07) College Bowl playoffs; (36:47) Baker Shakespeare Festival; (39:35) Space Shuttle; (40:14) Eddie Speer of the Rice Food Committee; (41:26) Reaganomics Forum. Speakers: Dave Collins, Ronald Reagan, Norm Lindsey, Jim Koenig, Greg Roberts, Debbie Gronke, Dan Borden, Stan Barber, Chris Kreidler, Rice Morefield, Steve Bailey, David Tuttle, Tony Munn, Eddie Speer, James Robison, Stephen Klineberg
    - Chicken Skin Music - Lucinda Williams, 1982-01-26; wrc08261 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Lucinda Williams performs and talks about how she got started, influences, early life, living in Houston, first album - "Ramblin'," "Happy Woman Blues," working with the Hemmer Ridge Mountain Boys, worst music venue, and album availability. Speakers: Lucinda Williams, David John Scribner
    - Up in the Air - Susan Clark and Nanda Duhe, 1982-02-11; wrc07242 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "Up in the Air," Vincent Uher talks to Dr. Susan Clark and Nanda Duhe about the Equal Rights Amendment. Speakers: Susan Clark, Nanda Duhe, Vincent Uher
    - Concert Band performance, 1982-02-18; wrc07314 (Box 15)
      Contents include: A performance by the MOB Concert Band. They perform works by Darius Milhaud, Leonard Bernstein, Paul Hindemith, among others.
    - Associates' Dinner - Walter Cronkite, 1982-02-20; wrc07211; 59418 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Walter Cronkite speaks at the Associates Dinner. He discusses retirement, his travels, NASA, foreign policy, and the state of journalism. Speakers: Walter Cronkite
    - Up in the Air - SA Candidate Forum, 1982-02-22; wrc07212 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Student Association candidates discuss their platforms and views. We deleted the radio music break in the middle of this recording. Speakers: David Hudson, Doug Gardner, Brent Nyquist, Preston Smith, Brendon Cahill, Terri Henriott, Beth Sinclair, Dan Hu, Tom Morgan, Marlon Boarnet
    - Chicken Skin Music - The Banded Geckos (2 reels), 1982-02-23; wrc08258_01; wrc08258_02 (Box 15)
    - To the Point - Art Few, 1982-03-09; wrc07213 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Art Few about severe weather. Speakers: Art Few, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Richard Smith, 1982-03-09; wrc07214 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Richard Smith about economic changes in China. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Richard Smith
    - To the Point - Robert Hall, 1982-03-09; wrc07215 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Robert Hall about how African slave culture merged with white culture. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Robert Hall
    - College Bowl Western Regionals, 1982-03-20; wrc07216; 59416 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Scott Hochberg moderates three games: Rice University vs. California State - Fresno, Rice University vs. Brigham Young University, and Rice University vs. California State - Fresno. Speakers: Matt Kemple, Ronald Mann, Michael Lewis, Susan Faust, Scott Hochberg
    - News Archive 4, 1982-03-26-1982-04-14; wrc07217; 59374 (Box 15)
      Contents include: (00:01) Parking changes for new Mudd Computer Science building; (00:34) Reaganomics forum; (01:49) Professors receiving promotions; (03:08) Alan Kiepper new professor; (05:16) 1982 Beer-Bike races; (06:39) SWC Golf Tournament results. Speakers: Mary Voswinkle, David Tuttle, Dave Collins, Alan Kiepper, Norman Hackerman, Jonathon Sadow
    - April Fool's Day programming, 1982-04-01; wrc07218; 59417 (Box 15)
      Contents include: These are satirical programs/skits aired on April 1, 1982. (00:01) Beside the Point; (07:43) Classic Classics Nouveaux; (12:41) KTRU editorial; (14:21) Norts Spews; (18:11) 5 o'clock snooze; (22:11) Hammond song; (22:55) April Fool's promo; (23:23) Kiss-ass rock n' roll; (23:39) PSA - Orphan orgy. Speakers: Scott Hochberg
    - Beer Bike, 1982-04-10; wrc07240 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Dave Collins and David Tuttle call the 1982 Beer Bike Men's race. Speakers: Dave Collins, David Tuttle
    - To the Point - Edward Dix, 1982-04-12; wrc07219 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Edward Dix about the war in El Salvador. Speakers: Edward Dix, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Ken Kennedy, 1982-04-12; wrc07220 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Ken Kennedy about growing presence of computers in society. Speakers: Ken Kennedy, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1982-04-12; wrc07221 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about new peace movement. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Stephen Klineberg
    - To the Point - Steve Klaine, 1982-04-12; wrc07222 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Steve Klaine about the problem with hydrilla. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Steve Klaine
    - To the Point - Don Huddle, 1982-05-04; wrc07223 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Don Huddle about undocumented workers and INS [Immigration and Naturalization Service] raids, part 1. Speakers: Don Huddle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Pat Reiff, 1982-05-04; wrc07224 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Pat Reiff about the mass transit system and environmental issues. Speakers: Scott Hochberg, Pat Reiff
    - To the Point - John Freeman, 1982-05-04; wrc07239 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. John Freeman about the future of space exploration and solar cells. Speakers: John Freeman, Scott Hochberg
    - Renaissance interview, 1982-05-05; wrc07225 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Ray Isle interviews members of the band Renaissance. Michael Dunford and Peter Gosling discuss the formation of the band, adding new members, touring, writing new music, and their new album and record label. Speakers: Ray Isle, Michael Dunford, Peter Gosling
    - Laurie Anderson interview, 1982-05-13; wrc07226 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Michael Zakes speaks to Laurie Anderson about her music, performances, electronic equipment in the studio and on-stage, getting radio airplay, changing record labels, recording next to an elevator shaft, favorite music, favorite writers, and her current tour. She also does a station ID. Speakers: Michael Zakes, Laurie Anderson
    - Chicken Skin Music - The Neville Brothers, 1982-05-18; wrc08255 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Art and Ivan Neville talk about new music, influences, New Orleans, "Fiyo On The Bayou," The Meters, and songwriting. Speakers: Art Neville, Ivan Neville, David John Scribner
    - Chicken Skin Music - The Banded Geckos, 1982-05-26; wrc08260 (Box 15)
    - To the Point - John Hughes, 1982-06-09; wrc07227 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. John Hughes about the insanity defense. Speakers: John Hughes, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Julie Taylor, 1982-06-09; wrc07228 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Julie Taylor about the Falkland Islands. Speakers: Julie Taylor, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Norman Hackerman, 1982-06-09; wrc07229 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Norman Hackerman about safeguarding U.S. academic intelligence from Russia. Speakers: Norman Hackerman, Scott Hochberg
    - Chicken Skin Music - Porky Cohen, 1982-06-13; wrc08257 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Porky Cohen and Roomful of Blues talk about their careers, influences, and new music. Speakers: David John Scribner, Porky Cohen
    - To the Point - Don Huddle, 1982-06-24; wrc07230 (Box 15)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Don Huddle about undocumented workers, part 2. Speakers: Don Huddle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Richard Stabell, 1982-06-24; wrc07231 (Box 15)
    - Roky Erickson interview, 1982-06-25; wrc07241 (Box 15)
      Contents include: Mark Linimon interviews Roky Erickson about his new album, meaning of his songs, and heavy metal. Speakers: Roky Erickson, Mark Linimon
  - Sub-Series: 1982/1983, 59400
    - The Beat interview, 1982-07-31; wrc08041 (Box 16)
      Contents include: Michael Zakes talks to David Wakeling and Andy Cox of The Beat, also known as The English Beat, about their cover tunes, their albums, touring, 2 Tone, ska, Saxa, politics, musical influences, switching record labels, S Concert, charities, and American food. They do a station ID. We deleted radio music. Speakers: Dave Wakeling, Andy Cox, Michael Zakes
    - To the Point - William Martin, 1982-08-05; wrc07244 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Bill Martin about the rapture. Speakers: William Martin, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Gaston Rimlinger, 1982-08-05; wrc07245 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Gaston Rimlinger about the balanced budget. Speakers: Gaston Rimlinger, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - John Bryant, 1982-08-05; wrc07246 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. John Bryant about the effects of high interest rates. Speakers: John Bryant, Scott Hochberg
    - News Archive 1, 1982-08-22-1982-09-21; wrc07247; 59408 (Box 16)
      Contents include: (00:01) Summer in review - Hackerman injured, Charles Duncan named head of Board of Governors, Josephine Abercrombie named Vice-President of Board of Governors, William D. Broyles named Editor-In-Chief of Newsweek, Lovett College storeroom robbed, New campus emergency telephone system, new camps police bicycle patrol, New buildings Mudd Building and Herring Hall, Iranian Riot and SMU, Margaret Fossi killer found - Coral Eugene Watts, Matriculation ceremonies, Casino Party and underage drinking, Dr. Don Benjamin faculty address, Wiess college pranks during Activities Fair; (11:55) Preview of SWC football season; (23:01) Graham Stebbings dies in auto accident; (24:08) Dr. William Akers on parking; (25:23) Classroom shortage; (26:16) Pres. Ronald Reagan on Lebanon and the PLO; (27:21) Graham Stebbings funeral arrangements; (28:01) Sports preview, annual SWC press tour; (32:31) Student election schedule; (33:41) Stadium scoreboard damaged by lightning; (34:32) James Groves' death; (35:27) John Cox, new Trustee; (36:30) Sports review/preview; (39:40) Sports review/preview; (42:56) Problems with Rice phone system; (44:02) Two reviews of Rice Players' "Major Barbara". Speakers: David Tuttle, Mary Voswinkle, Jonathan Sadow, Katherine Brown, Mary Ellen Trunko, Norman Lindsey, William Akers, Dave Collins, Ronald Reagan, Don Benjamin, Jeff Long, Kathy Brown, Lynn Boyden
    - To the Point - Gordon Smith, 1982-09-08; wrc07248 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Gordon Smith about economic protectionism. Speakers: Gordon Smith, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Ed Miller, 1982-09-19; wrc07249 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Ed Miller about large corporate structures and their efficiency. Speakers: Ed Miller, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Doug Tuggle, 1982-09-20; wrc07250 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Doug Tuggle about the economic recovery. Speakers: Doug Tuggle, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - Elizabeth Long, 1982-09-20; wrc07251 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. Elizabeth Long about how women perform in traditionally male jobs. Speakers: Elizabeth Long, Scott Hochberg
    - To the Point - John Boles, 1982-09-20; wrc07252 (Box 16)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Scott Hochberg talks to Dr. John Boles about writing corporate histories. Speakers: John Boles, Scott Hochberg
    - President's Lecture Series - George Thomas, 1982-09-21; wrc08043 (Box 16)
      Contents include: As part of the President's Lecture Series, the Right Honourable the Viscount of Tonypandy Thomas George Thomas speaks on parliamentary democracy in his address entitled "Parliamentary Democracy in the Space Age." Speakers: George Thomas
    - News Archive 2, 1982-09-23-1982-11-04; wrc07253; 59409 (Box 16)